The next thing we're going to do is make it to our apple and project our if they collide with each other,
they're going to destroy each other.
Right now, they kind of just ignore each other.
It'll be kind of cool if when they both hit each other, they both get destroyed.
So in order to achieve this effect, if we just open up our Apple product to.
And currently we've made it so that if our apple hit something which has a type called enemy will destroy
it.
So in order to make it so that when my apple hits the projectile, it gets destroyed.
I want us to go over to our projectile blueprint and select it and add a tag.
Only to add a tag called Project Projectile.
And then if we head back to our Apple blueprint, just drag off of actor and look for actor as tag.
And here on the tag, look for projectile.
So the first thing we're going to do is check to see if the actor that we overlap has the enemy tag.
If it doesn't, we're going to check to see if the actor that we overlapped has the projectile tag.
If that is true, then we're going to destroy this actor to just wrap up here.
Whoops.
So just drag up here and look for destroy actor.
And then after we've done that, we're going to destroy this actor to look for destroy actor and then
go compile and save.
So now I go play and through my apple when the mushroom goes is projectile.
It should cancel each other out.
Whoops.
Looks like nothing happened.
And I think I know the reason why we just made it so that the apple ignore anything with the collision
while dynamic.
If I go to my projector and set the sphere, its collision is probably, well, dynamic.
So let's go down.
Go here.
Yep.
It's collision is well dynamic.
So in order to get around this, I'm just going to change this.
So I go custom and I'm going to change this object type to be, well, static.
And now I go compile and play.
And treat my protector.
When he shoots his, they cancel each other out.
Nice.